Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Bronx Dogs - Mission to free; Tribute to Jazzy Jay, 2000; SR-13335; Bronx Dogs (Box 198)
          Catalog # HVN9412P; A-side Matrix # HVN 9412P A
          Heavenly
        - B.B. & Q. Band - Immagination, 1982; SR-12239; B.B. & Q. Band (Box 198)
          Catalog # SPRO-9805; A-side Matrix # SPRO 9805-98172-Z1
        - B.B. & Q. Band - (I'm a) dreamer, 1986; SR-12240; B.B. & Q. Band (Box 198)
          Catalog # ED 5160; A-side Matrix # STED-66844-A1
        - B.B. & Q. Band - On the beat, 1981; SR-13336; B.B. & Q. Band (Box 198)
          In same jacket as # SR-13337. 2 copies
          Catalog # SPRO-9645; A-side Matrix # SPRO1-9645 A
        - B.B. & Q. Band - On the beat, 1981; SR-13337; B.B. & Q. Band (Box 198)
          In same jacket as # SR-13336. 2 copies
        - Brooklyn Dreams - Street Man, 1978; SR-13338; Brooklyn Dreams (Box 198)
          Catalog # MND20613; A-side Matrix # MND-20613 a
          Milenium
        - Brooklyn Express - Do it again (Medley with Billy Jean), 1983; SR-13339; Brooklyn Express (Box 198)
          Catalog # BC-4020-A; A-side Matrix # BR-1983-3-A
        - Brooklyn Express - Hollywood Party (Getting High), 1979; SR-13340; Brooklyn Express (Box 198)
          Catalog # BC 4002; A-side Matrix # BC-4002
        - Brooklyn Funk Essentials - We got to come together (test pressing), 1988; SR-12241; Brooklyn Funk Essentials (Box 198)
          Test pressing
          Catalog # MIN 4; A-side Matrix # CR-7877-11 A
          Minimal Records
        - Brooklyn Queens - Amanda, 2002; SR-12242; Brooklyn Queens (Box 199)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # AMANDA-A
          Paragon Music Group
        - Brooklyn Queens - Amanda, 2002; SR-13341; Brooklyn Queens (Box 199)
          Catalog # TB-2381-0; A-side Matrix # TB2381-0A
          Tommy Boy Silver Label
        - Brooks, Mel - To be or not to be (the Hitler rap), 1983; SR-12243; Brooks, Mel (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12244. 2 copies
          Catalog # AN 810; A-side Matrix # AN-810-A
        - Brooks, Mel - To be or not to be (the Hitler rap), 1983; SR-12244; Brooks, Mel (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12243. 2 copies
        - Brooks, Mel - It's good to be king, 1982; SR-12245; Brooks, Mel (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12246. 2 copies
          Catalog # 4W9 02761; A-side Matrix # 4W9-02761AS-1B
          WMOT Records
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Brooks, Mel - It's good to be king, 1982; SR-12246; Brooks, Mel (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12245. 2 copies
        - Brooks, Pattie - Get it on and have a party, 1979; SR-12247; Brooks, Pattie (Box 199)
          Catalog # L33-1123; A-side Matrix # MCA-3604-PL1
        - Brooks, Pattie - Got tu go disco, 1979; SR-12248; Brooks, Pattie (Box 199)
          Catalog # NBD 20188; A-side Matrix # NBD20188-ASXX A-J
          Casablanca
        - Brookins, Robert - Our lives, 1980; SR-12249; Brookins, Robert (Box 199)
          Catalog # MCA-23681; A-side Matrix # MCA-6156-FDS-1
        - Terry Brooks & Strange - High flyer, 1981; SR-13342; Terry Brooks & Strange (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-13343. 2 copies
          Catalog # S.P.R. 0013; A-side Matrix # SPR-0013-3-EARTH
          Star People Records Inc.
          Casselberry, Florida
        - Terry Brooks & Strange - High flyer, 1981; SR-13343; Terry Brooks & Strange (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-13342. 2 copies
        - Terry Brooks & Strange - To Earth with love, 1980; SR-13344; Terry Brooks & Strange (Box 199)
          Catalog # SPR0005; A-side Matrix # SPR0005-A-RE-01
        - Bros - The time, 1989; SR-12250; Bros (Box 199)
          Catalog # E 45390; A-side Matrix # AL 45390-1A
        - Bros - When will I be famous?, 1988; SR-12251; Bros (Box 199)
          Catalog # 49 07826; A-side Matrix # XSS177802-1A
        - Brotha Lynch Hung - R.I.P., 1995; SR-12252; Brotha Lynch Hung (Box 199)
          Catalog # SPRO 50854; A-side Matrix # SPRO-50854-A
          Black Market Records
          Sacramento, California
        - Brothers Johnson - Stomp; Get the funk out my face; So fine; Dynomite, 1987; SR-12253; Brothers Johnson; Johnson, Howard; Tony Camillo's Bazuka (Box 199)
          Catalog # OG 4011; A-side Matrix # OG-4011-A
          Old Gold
        - Brothers From Another Planet - Wishing on a star (test pressing), 1990; SR-12254; Brothers From Another Planet (Box 199)
          Catalog # SAM5010; A-side Matrix # SAM 5010 A
          Sam Records
        - Brother D - Clappers powers, 1987; SR-12255; Brother D (Box 199)
          Catalog # CL-12-0008; A-side Matrix # CL-12-0008-A
          Clappers Records
        - Brother 07 - It's my world, 1990; SR-12256; Brother 07 (Box 199)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # 0007 A RE
          Def Boy Records
        - Brother Arthur - What you gonna do; Year of the 9, 1994; SR-12257; Brother Arthur (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12258. 2 copies
          Catalog # NUCY 100; A-side Matrix # NUCY-100-A
          C-YA Entertainment
        - Brother Arthur - What you gonna do; Year of the 9, 1994; SR-12258; Brother Arthur (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12257. 2 copies
        - Brother Beyond - The girl I used to know, 1990; SR-12259; Brother Beyond (Box 199)
          Catalog # SPRO 04545; A-side Matrix # SPRO-4545-A-Z1-DMM
          EMI
        - Brother Beyond - The girl I used to know, 1990; SR-12260; Brother Beyond (Box 199)
        - Brother D - How we gonna make the black nation rise?, 1980; SR-12261; Brother D; Collective Effort (Box 199)
          Catalog # 12 BRW 24; A-side Matrix # 12 BRW 24 A-1U-1-1
          4th and Broadway
        - Brother Greene - The God, 2004; SR-12262; Brother Greene (Box 199)
          Catalog # SR-004; A-side Matrix # SR-004-LP-A
          God Sheise Music
        - Brother to Brother - Monster jam (I want to funk with you), 1981; SR-12263; Brother to Brother (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12264. 2 copies
          Catalog # SH-560; A-side Matrix # VID-208-A
          Sugar Hill Records
        - Brother to Brother - Monster jam (I want to funk with you), 1981; SR-12264; Brother to Brother (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12263. 2 copies
        - Brotherhood - The surge, 1988; SR-12265; Brotherhood; Toxic Twin; Lars B (Box 199)
          Catalog # BLISS-009; A-side Matrix # BLISS 009 A
          Bliss
        - Brotherhood II - Losing my way, SR-12266; Brotherhood II (Box 199)
          Catalog # KAM 008 A; A-side Matrix # KAM 008 A
          Kamtschatka
        - Brotherhood Creed - 50/50 love, 1992; SR-12267; Brotherhood Creed (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12268. 2 copies
          Catalog # GAS8P 2372; A-side Matrix # GAS 11387 FDS-1
          Gasoline Alley Records
        - Brotherhood Creed - 50/50 love, 1992; SR-12268; Brotherhood Creed (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12267. 2 copies
        - Brothers Grimm - I.C.O.K. MC's; In N out, 1996; SR-12269; Brothers Grimm (Box 199)
          Catalog # HRX 8601-1; A-side Matrix # HRX-2311-A
          Hurricane Records
        - Brothers in Rhythm - Forever and a day, 1994; SR-12270; Brothers in Rhythm; Charvoni (Box 199)
          Catalog # 49 77619; A-side Matrix # XSS-77619-A-1A
          Epic Dance
        - Brothers Johnson - Blam!! Radio special, 1978; SR-12271; Brothers Johnson (Box 199)
          Catalog # SP-17077; A-side Matrix # A&MSP 17077-M2
        - Brothers Johnson - Kickin', 1988; SR-12272; Brothers Johnson (Box 199)
          Catalog # SP-5162; A-side Matrix # SPO 5162-A ES1
        - Brothers Johnson - Dancin' free, 1981; SR-12273; Brothers Johnson (Box 199)
          Catalog # SP-17170; A-side Matrix # A&M-SP-017170-B-S1
        - Brothers Johnson - Stomp!, 1980; SR-12274; Brothers Johnson (Box 199)
          Catalog # SP-17111; A-side Matrix # A&MSPO17111A-SM1
        - Brothers Johnson - You keep me coming back, 1984; SR-12275; Brothers Johnson (Box 199)
          Catalog # SP-12102; A-side Matrix # A&M SPO012102A-ES1
        - Brothers Like Outlaw - Trapped into darkness, 1992; SR-12276; Brothers Like Outlaw (Box 199)
          Catalog # 422-864 187-1; A-side Matrix # 422-864-187-1-AS/SP
        - Brothers of a New Nature - Just like me, 1992; SR-12277; Brothers of a New Nature (Box 199)
          Catalog # BONN1; A-side Matrix # BONN-1-A
          New Nature Records
        - Brothers of Peace - Work it out, 1998; SR-12278; Brothers of Peace (Box 199)
          Catalog # SOW-418; A-side Matrix # SOW-418-A
        - Brothers of the Mind - Stop schemin'; Kick facts, 1995; SR-12279; Brothers of the Mind (Box 199)
          Catalog # MXN-3010; A-side Matrix # MXN-3010-A
          Max'n
        - Brothers Unique - School daze, 1981; SR-12280; Brothers Unique (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12281. 2 copies
          Catalog # SUD 005; A-side Matrix # SUD-005-A
          Sutra
        - Brothers Unique - School daze, 1981; SR-12281; Brothers Unique (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12280. 2 copies
        - Brothers Unique - School daze, 1981; SR-13345; Brothers Unique (Box 199)
          Catalog # GHT-414; A-side Matrix # GHT-414-A
          Glad-Hamp Records
        - Brothers Uv Da Blackmarket - Not u again, 1992; SR-12282; Brothers Uv Da Blackmarket (Box 199)
          Catalog # 0-66362; A-side Matrix # 0-66362-A
          Select
        - Brown, Bobby - My prerogative (extended remix), 1988; SR-12283; Brown, Bobby (Box 199)
          Catalog # MCA-23888; A-side Matrix # MCA8133-FDS-2
        - Brown, Bobby - Girl next door (extended remix), 1980; SR-12284; Brown, Bobby (Box 199)
          Catalog # MCA-23720; A-side Matrix # MCA6600-FDS-2
        - Brown, Bobby - Seventeen (extended club remix), 1987; SR-12285; Brown, Bobby (Box 199)
          Catalog # MCA-23772; A-side Matrix # MCA7001-FDS-1
        - Brown, Bobby - Roni, 1988; SR-12286; Brown, Bobby (Box 199)
          Catalog # L33-17719; A-side Matrix # MCA-8473-FDS-1
        - Brown, Bobby - Good enough, 1992; SR-12287; Brown, Bobby (Box 199)
          Catalog # MCA8P 2483; A-side Matrix # MCA-11480 HF2
        - Brown, Chuck - That'll work (2001), 1988; SR-12288; Brown, Chuck; Soul Searchers (Box 199)
          Catalog # IHY-1003; A-side Matrix # IHY-1003-A
          I Hear Ya! Records
        - Brown, Chuck - That'll work (2001), 1988; SR-12289; Brown, Chuck; Soul Searchers (Box 199)
        - Brown, Chuck - Live '87 (Disc one), 1987; SR-12290; Brown, Chuck; Soul Searchers (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12291. Double album
          Catalog # MELT LP3; A-side Matrix # MELTLP-3-A
          Flame Records
        - Brown, Chuck - Live '87 (Disc two), 1987; SR-12291; Brown, Chuck; Soul Searchers (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-12290. Double album
          Catalog # MELT LP3; A-side Matrix # MELTLP-3-C
        - Brown, Chuck - Be-bumpin-fresh, 1985; SR-13346; Brown, Chuck (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-13347. 2 copies
          Catalog # F 0008; A-side Matrix # F-0008-A
          Future Records & Tapes
        - Brown, Chuck - Be-bumpin-fresh, 1985; SR-13347; Brown, Chuck (Box 199)
          In same jacket as # SR-13346. 2 copies
        - Chuck Brown & the Soul Searchers - We need some money, 1984; SR-13348; Chuck Brown & the Soul Searchers; Brown, Chuck (Box 200)
          Catalog # TDE-3004; A-side Matrix # TDE-3004-A
        - Chuck Brown & the Soul Searchers - Run Joe, 1986; SR-13349; Chuck Brown & the Soul Searchers; Brown, Chuck (Box 200)
          Catalog # F-0015; A-side Matrix # F-0015-A
        - Brown, Dennis - Home sweet home; Going home, 1979; SR-12761; Brown, Dennis; Pappa Iron & Dubwise (Box 200)
          Catalog # PD 0168A; A-side Matrix # PD0168A
          Papa D Records
        - Brown, Dennis - Get high on your love, 1982; SR-12762; Brown, Dennis (Box 200)
          Catalog # SP-17206; A-side Matrix # AM SP 017206-A
        - Brown, Djinji - Mojuba, 2002; SR-12763; Brown, Djinji (Box 200)
          Catalog # SVH-016-1; A-side Matrix # SVH-016-1 A
          Seven Heads
        - Brown, Foxy - Big bad mamma; Never seen before, 1997; SR-13300; Brown, Foxy; Dru Hill; EPMD (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13301. 2 copies
          Catalog # 574 979-1; A-side Matrix # 574 979-1
        - Brown, Foxy - Big bad mamma; Never seen before, 1997; SR-13301; Brown, Foxy; Dru Hill; EPMD (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13300. 2 copies
        - Brown, Foxy - Candy, 2001; SR-13302; Brown, Foxy; Kelis (Box 200)
          Catalog # DEFR 15394-1; A-side Matrix # 314-588-738-1-A-1
        - Brown, Foxy - Ill Na Na (Disc one), 1996; SR-13303; Brown, Foxy (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13304. Double album
          Catalog # 314 533 684-1; A-side Matrix # 314-533-961-1-A
        - Brown, Foxy - Ill Na Na (Disc two), 1996; SR-13304; Brown, Foxy (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13303. Double album
          Catalog # 314 533 684-1; A-side Matrix # 314-533-962-1-A
        - Brown, Foxy - Big bad mamma; Never seen before, 1997; SR-13305; Brown, Foxy; Dru Hill; EPMD (Box 200)
          Catalog # 574 985-1; A-side Matrix # 574 985-1 A
        - Brown, Foxy - Come fly with me, 2005; SR-13306; Brown, Foxy; Sizzla (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13307. Different discs
          Catalog # DEFR 16630-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-16630-1-A
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - DMX - Give 'em what they want; Pump ya fist, 2005; SR-13307; DMX; Swizz Beatz (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13306. Different discs
          Catalog # DEFR 16267-1; A-side Matrix # B0004938-11-B
        - Brown, James - Feelin' James, SR-13308; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Includes vocals of an unknown artist
          Catalog # T.D. 802; A-side Matrix # TD-802-A
          T.D. Records, Inc.
        - Brown, James - It's too funky in here, 1979; SR-13309; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # PRO 086; A-side Matrix # PRO-086-79-NP-4203-3-G.D
        - Brown, James - Rapp Payback (Where iz Moses), 1980; SR-13310; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13311. 2 copies
          Catalog # TKD-452; A-side Matrix # TKD-452-A
          T.K. Records
        - Brown, James - Rapp Payback (Where iz Moses), 1980; SR-13311; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13310. 2 copies
        - Brown, James - Funky men; Mashed potatoes, 1981; SR-13312; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # TK-465; A-side Matrix # TKD-465-A
        - Brown, James - Hell (Disc one), 1974; SR-13350; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # PD 2-9001; A-side Matrix # PD-2-9001-A
        - Brown, James - Can I get some help; Get it together, 2005; SR-13351; Brown, James; James Brown Orchestra (Box 200)
          Catalog # JB-105; A-side Matrix # JB 105 A
          King Records
        - Brown, James - Funk lord chapter 2, SR-13352; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # FL-5403; A-side Matrix # FL4503-A
        - Brown, James - The payback mix (keep on doing what you're doing but make it funky), 1988; SR-13353; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # URBX 17; A-side Matrix # URBX-17-A1
          Urban
        - Brown, James - Sex machine (Disc one), 1970; SR-13354; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13355. Double album
          Catalog # PD-2-9004; A-side Matrix # PD-2-9004-AS-CPX
        - Brown, James - Sex machine (Disc two), 1970; SR-13355; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13354. Double album
          Catalog # PD-2-9004; A-side Matrix # PD-2-9004-CS-CPX
        - Brown, James - This is … James Brown, 1967; SR-13356; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # 6336 201; A-side Matrix # 6336201 2Y
          Phillips
        - Brown, James - Live in New York (Disc one), 1983; SR-13357; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13358. Double album
          Catalog # 64005; A-side Matrix # 64005 A
        - Brown, James - Live in New York (Disc two), 1983; SR-13358; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13357. Double album
          Catalog # 64005; A-side Matrix # 64005 C
        - Brown, James - If you don't give a dogone about it, 1977; SR-13359; Brown, James; J.B.'s (Box 200)
          Catalog # PRO 038; A-side Matrix # PRO-038-77-NP-2845-6-GD
        - Brown, James - James Brown & friends - soul session live, 1989; SR-13360; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # 7461 45164; A-side Matrix # PAL-45164-1A
        - Brown, James - Revolution of the mind (Disc one), 1971; SR-13438; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13439. Double album
          Catalog # PD 3003; A-side Matrix # PD 3003-A
        - Brown, James - Revolution of the mind (Disc two), 1971; SR-13439; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13438. Double album
          Catalog # PD 3003; A-side Matrix # PD 3003-C
        - Brown, James - Ultimate remixes, 2003; SR-13440; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13441. Different discs
          Catalog # UM3J-4010; A-side Matrix # UM3J-4010-1A
          Japan
        - Brown, James - The ultimate remixes, 2003; SR-13441; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13440. Different discs
          Catalog # JAMES 1; A-side Matrix # JAMES 1 A
          Not On Label (James Brown)
        - Brown, James - Gravity, 1986; SR-13361; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # Z 40380; A-side Matrix # AL-40380-1C
        - Brown, James - In the jungle groove (Disc one), 1986; SR-13362; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13363. Double album
          Catalog # 422-829-624-1 Y-2; A-side Matrix # 422-829-624-1-AS-HRM
        - Brown, James - In the jungle groove (Disc two), 1986; SR-13363; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13362. Double album
          Catalog # 422-829-624-1 Y-2; A-side Matrix # 422-829-624-1-CS-HRM
        - Brown, James - Bring it on!, 1983; SR-13364; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13365. Different discs
          Catalog # CAS22001; A-side Matrix # CR-22001-ARMI-3
          Churchill / Augusta Records Inc.
          Tulsa, Oklahoma
        - Air Force 1 - See the light; Feel the heat, 1984; SR-13365; Air Force 1 (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13364. Different discs
          Catalog # SW 2238; A-side Matrix # SW-2238-A
          Streetwise
        - Brown, James - Motherlode (Disc one), 2001; SR-13366; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13367. Double album
          Catalog # SVLP 314; A-side Matrix # 08-46173-20A-SVLP-314
        - Brown, James - Motherlode (Disc two), 2001; SR-13367; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13366. Double album
          Catalog # SVLP 314; A-side Matrix # 08-46173-20C-SVLP-314
        - Brown, James - The best of James Brown, 1981; SR-13368; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # PD-1-6340; A-side Matrix # PD-1-6340-AS-PW
        - Brown, James - I'm real, 1988; SR-13369; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # INT 147.331; A-side Matrix # DMMc-2084 A-1/3-88
          Stuttgart, Germany
        - Brown, James - Can't get any harder (Disc one), 1993; SR-13370; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13371. Double album
          Catalog # 72392 75352-1; A-side Matrix # S-27371
        - Brown, James - Can't get any harder (Disc two), 1993; SR-13371; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13370. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # 72392 75352-1; A-side Matrix # S-27373
        - Brown, James - I'm real, 1988; SR-13372; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # Z 44241; A-side Matrix # AL-44241-1A
        - Brown, James - Live at Chastian Park (Disc one), 1988; SR-13373; Brown, James; Soul G's (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13374. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # JAM 1984; A-side Matrix # JAM-1984A
          Charly Groove
        - Brown, James - Live at Chastian Park (Disc two), 1988; SR-13374; Brown, James; Soul G's (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13373. Double album. Annotated
          Catalog # JAM 1984; A-side Matrix # JAM-1984C
        - Brown, James - Love over-due, 1991; SR-13375; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # 72392 75225; A-side Matrix # 72392 75225-1A
        - Brown, James - Hooked On Brown, Part 1 (The Platinum Hits Medley), 1996; SR-13376; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # 72392 78094-0; A-side Matrix # 72392 78094-0-A
        - Brown, James - The James Brown special, 1983; SR-13377; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # 2417 351; A-side Matrix # 2417 351 S1
        - Brown, James - Get on the good foot (Disc one), 1972; SR-13378; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13379. Double album
          Catalog # PD-2-3004; A-side Matrix # PD2 3004-A
        - Brown, James - Get on the good foot (Disc two), 1972; SR-13379; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13378. Double album
          Catalog # PD-2-3004; A-side Matrix # PD2 3004-C
        - Brown, James - Say it loud- I'm black and I'm proud, 1969; SR-13380; Brown, James (Box 200)
          Catalog # KS-1047; A-side Matrix # COL-KS1047-A
          Cincinatti, Ohio
        - Brown, James - Soul mastercuts, SR-13381; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13382. 2 copies
          Catalog # SMLP-561; A-side Matrix # SMLP-561-A
          Soul Mastercuts, Ltd.
        - Brown, James - Soul mastercuts, SR-13382; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13381. 2 copies
        - Brown, James - Time to get busy, 1988; SR-13383; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13384. Different discs
          Catalog # 4Z9 08130; A-side Matrix # XSS-08130-A-1A
        - Brown, James - Static, 1988; SR-13384; Brown, James (Box 200)
          In same jacket as # SR-13383. Different discs
          Catalog # 4Z9 07863; A-side Matrix # XSS-07863A-1B
        - Brown, James - Say it loud, "I'm black and I'm proud" the hip-hop remix, 1991; SR-13385; Brown, James (Box 201)
          Catalog # 867 353-1; A-side Matrix # 867-353-1-BS-SP
        - Brown, James - Cold sweat, SR-13386; Brown, James; Famous Flames (Box 201)
          Catalog # PD 1020; A-side Matrix # 3972 PD 1020-1A 340518
        - Brown, James - Cold Sweat, 2004; SR-13387; Brown, James; J.B.'s (Box 201)
          Catalog # JB102; A-side Matrix # JB102A
        - Brown, James - Soul power parts 1 & 2; Give it up or turn it, 2001; SR-13388; Brown, James (Box 201)
          Catalog # S12DJ-046; A-side Matrix # 08 47925 20 1A1 S12 DJ 046
          Simply Vinyl (S12)
        - Brown, James - Respect me, 1995; SR-13389; Brown, James (Box 201)
          Catalog # 72392 78034-1; A-side Matrix # 72392 78034-1-A
        - Brown, Jocelyn - Ego maniac, 1987; SR-13390; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 201)
          Catalog # 0-20469; A-side Matrix # 0-20469-A-CHI
        - Brown, Jocelyn - One from the heart, 1987; SR-13391; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 201)
          Catalog # 1-25445; A-side Matrix # 1-25445A-SH2
        - Brown, Jocelyn - Somebody else's guy, 1984; SR-13392; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 201)
          Catalog # VND DJ1 BS; A-side Matrix # VND D01 B
          Vinyl Dream Records
        - Raven - So in love, 1984; SR-13393; Raven; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 201)
          Catalog # SC25; A-side Matrix # SC-25-A
          Silver Cloud Records
        - Brown, Jocelyn - Somebody else's guy, 1984; SR-13394; Brown, Jocelyn (Box 201)
          Catalog # SPEC 1342; A-side Matrix # SPEC-1342-A
          Quebec, Canada
        - Brown, Kathy - I appreciate, 1995; SR-13395; Brown, Kathy (Box 201)